|||||\\\\\\\\\\\\\
Alchemy
Shower
Thank you for showing everything
- I'm waiting for your decision
- Yes
This place is right between Jinyowon and Sosnovy Bor
Tiles and floors are good
This is the best option we've seen
Don't you think there are too many rooms?
They will have children soon
The son will take the surname Pak and head Sosnovy Bor
The daughter will take the surname Jin and lead Jinyeowon
They should give birth to more
It's good that I asked you to join me
I will choose the house that you like
To be honest,
I wouldn't like to live in a big house
I like a cozy house
where my husband and I will live happily
With a small garden where you can plant your favorite flowers
You love flowers so much
Maybe plant balsam?
My husband and I would paint our nails with paints from it*
*balsam root was crushed and used to color nails and fingertips yellow
It would be great to live like this
I'll look for you
such a house
What?
I will buy a house with a small garden
and I will plant balsam
This will be my gift
for your wedding
Gift?
Master Li loved Sapsari so much
I'll give you a puppy too
Are you marrying me to Master Li now?
Project coordinator and editor: Ria_Lee
You said you were happy just looking at him
Assistant coordinators: Martini, gaarysn
Typesetter translators: Ria_Lee, Mina_Mi
Do you think I was happy looking at Master Li?
I'm not completely stupid
That is, you will generously give me a house,
what if I marry Master Li?
I have money for such a gift
Do you know
buy me a house with a hundred rooms
One hundred?
So you like big houses?
Still, I'm a little slow-witted
Are you a fool?
Feelings for you made me happy
I was hoping
you will understand sooner or later
Cooked your favorite dishes, sewed your clothes
Although you are slow, I hoped that one day
it will come to you
Are you passing me off as someone else?
Are you giving me a house for my wedding to someone else?
Maid Kim...
I didn't understand...
Shut up!
Choosing a house together
I imagined how we would get married,
how we will paint each other's nails in love
balsam flowers,
who picked in the garden
In love?
Yes! In love!
Love is a carrot!
In love!
Yes! Exactly! In love!
This picture is so vivid before my eyes
Forget it
You shattered my dreams
I won't expect anything more from you
But I will accept a house with a hundred rooms!
I...
Maid Kim!
Maid Kim
In love...
I ruined everything
Idiot
Excellent
I'll marry someone
Let him give me a home!
There you are
Maid Kim, are you crying?
No. Why should I cry?
Are you crying? Who upset?
Your tears break my heart
I'm just jealous
that Mr. Dan Gu will get married before you
I'm jealous and sad
No need to be sad. I'm getting married soon
What?
Have you finally decided to marry someone?
Yes, so there is no reason for envy and sadness
Then...
Then you should leave it
What is this?
Gifts for your wedding that I kept
I thought about giving them to Mr. Dan Gu and Ms. Cho Yeon
Why give it to them? A waste
Yes?
Should I give them to Mrs. Huo?
Why does she need it?
You said you were getting married
I know everything
She is your egg
- My egg?
- Your secret lover
Egg of a graceful heron on a treetop
Maid Kim, you misunderstood. This is not the same bird
- Isn't that her?
- No
I thought she would hatch from an egg
There is someone else, then?
Yes. Yes
And who is it?
Maid Kim, don't be surprised
And if you can't restrain yourself,
bite your handkerchief
Who could it be?
There were no other girls near you
Really...
Yes. Moo Deok will get it all
It can't be
How is that? What about Mrs. Ho?
I see things are going well between you and Mr. Chan Wook.
Yes
I decided to marry him
I like to spread all sorts of rumors
Please. Let everyone know that I changed my destiny
The news of your wedding will clear up all the obscene rumors
"Indecent rumors"?
Many people gossiped that he was impotent,
times chastity practices
This is not true
That's what everyone said. This is wrong?
Not a word of truth!
So you checked it yourself
What are you talking about?
It's clear. And that's why I decided to marry him
What kind of woman would marry an impotent man?
even if he is a rich heir?
Don't worry
Rest assured, I'll tell everyone
"She checked, he is not impotent"
We haven't slept together yet!
We really haven't had anything yet
Don't be shy. I'm older
You were so mean when we first met
And now there, a heart has appeared
I thought that one day you would break off relations with everyone and disappear
I told you I changed fate
I will stay and protect those I love
Apparently you like him a lot
I wish you to live happily
I will pick up a sword that will help you destroy Chan Wook
Only I can protect you by saving you from the King's star
Chan Wook lost all his strength
Gave all my energy to destroy the barrier
He can't become the next Gwangju
He lost his influence
And everyone thinks that the King's star has shone for me
You have nothing to offer me, Deputy Gwangju
Chang Gan sacrificed himself in the name of
Pine Forest, Jinyeowon and Jeonbugwan
But Jin Woo Tak is alive, you will be found guilty
I don't want to punish my former teacher
Make it clear and accept the punishment
Do you really think the stone has disappeared?
Ice stone is filled with heavenly energy
Born under the star of the King
endowed with this power
What will you do
if Chang Wook is hiding this power?
I'll be waiting for your answer
I will always be faithful to you, Your Highness
You came to your senses, but you continue to remain silent?
I saved you only so that you could atone for your sins
in front of our daughter
Before Boo Young
When we first met
I fell in love with your warm smile
That's cute too
I think this will suit our Boo Young
And from the moment we met,
in love with you
I didn't love anyone
except
I'm trying to make things clear to you
I say this so that you suffer
I want you to know
deceived Jin Mu, you did this to our daughter
I hope you suffer
Jin Woo Tak in Saejukwon
He came to his senses
Since he's alive,
he will probably betray me and our organization
We need to get rid of him
I brought the ashes of the queen's souls
and bells, as you ordered
I can make all the nomads go crazy
If Chang Wook has the power of an ice stone,
he will have to show them
Make them two rings
You ordered two rings
So the rumors don't lie
These are rings for a wedding, do everything well
Of course
I'll do everything in the best possible way
Take a look at these options
Which one do you like?
These are beautiful
No!
This...
It belonged to Mrs. Young Ok
- Oh, no, not these
- Okay
They're not very
- And this?
- No...
Well...
- Madam Seo Jong...
- Not the same either
I don't like anything
I will remove those that do not suit you
These...
And these
Here
Choose from the rest
Seven rings?
Wait
It didn't seem like it was seven. I really don't remember anyone
Were they like Cho Young?
Promised to marry if the gates of energy were opened?
I swear I didn't look after them first
You yourself said that you need to make an effort not to fall in love with a handsome man.
They didn't try hard enough
Don't make me angry
Now I'm all yours
Aren't you proud that
went around everyone and got my heart?
If there were a dozen of them, I would be proud
Well, it's just funny
Do you think there weren't that many of them?
I'm kidding. You're the only one
I forgot everyone
Wait a minute
I saw several rings when I was cleaning your room
We need to find them
Why look for rings that no one needs?
I'm sure there were about a dozen of them.
Need to check
I don't have anyone
Moo Deok, let's eat
Tell me honestly
How many rings?
One
I will hold your hand in the ring of my arms
No one has a ring like this
Well...
Since we already have rings,
there is no need to make them from jade either
Maybe make some necklaces?
As you wish
I don't envy Dan Gu one bit
- I don’t envy Cho Young one bit
- So the rumors are true
This mischievous gentleman... smiles
You're right
Apparently I was from the very beginning
I misunderstood everything. Such a shame
Madam,
just don’t say that you confessed your feelings to him in that barrier
I was going to. I almost confessed
I had a chance
You don't have to hold a candle next to me
You can put it somewhere
Are you embarrassed that I'm here?
I'm happy with everything
Well, as you know
When you were lying in a drunken stupor in Sejukwon,
my advances didn't bother you
I thought you were Moo Deok
This is how he is next to his beloved
If Mr. Uk had suffered instead of Mr. Yulya,
you would get closer
You treat the wounded
Do you think so?
If he had been wounded,
Would I have a chance?
Seo Yul, I heard you are returning to Soho Fortress
Yes, after Dan Gu's wedding
Shall we have a party before you leave?
Yes
Your wound has healed but you are still in pain?
I thought it would get better, but I was wrong
Something else happened while I was unconscious
lay in the barrier?
We stopped the bleeding
Escaped So Yi gave you her blood
You can't donate blood like that
Why such recklessness?
I just
wanted to save him
Her blood got into your wound
But this shouldn't cause any problems
I think I'll get better soon
Don't want the heads to worry so keep it a secret
Okay, to the bottom!
Hey, what are you doing there?
What did you steal?
What is this?
Hey! Stop!
The wound left by the worm heals very slowly
That worm in his body
He's probably in pain
He needs the medicine I took in Jinyeowon
Moo Deok
You shouldn't work here anymore
What? Are you kicking me out?
If so, would you listen to me?
- No
- I knew it wasn't
Don't make me a bad person
Don't do housework anymore
You will be his beloved wife, I can't force you to work
So you accept me?
Do I have a choice? He just adores you
I won't call you mistress
I won't consider you my mother-in-law either.
Why should I be your mother-in-law if I myself am not yet married?
It would hurt my pride
Indeed
But you and the head will get married soon, right?
I thought you liked each other
Maid Kim...
Even you noticed it, but he didn’t
- Well...
- That is...
How can he be so slow-witted?
Is he close-minded or what?
He's just a fool
Yes! In love! Love is a carrot!
I can't
forget the words
which she said
me
Chapter
Uk...
When did you arrive?
Recently. I wanted to tell you something
Why are you so worried?
Something terrible
worries me
What did you want to say?
You see...
I plan to leave the capital for a while after Dan Gu's wedding.
How's that?
Then...
And the maid Kim?
If no one wants her to stay, I'll have to take her with me.
I don't know when we'll be back. Maybe in a year, or maybe in ten
Or maybe we will never return
I did something
unforgivable
If I keep her here
Do you think she will stay?
She...
cried
She will cry harder if you don't stop her
I'll leave
with the young master
I won't leave
I'll leave
There's no point in staying. Need to go
I want something
show you
These are balsam seeds
If you plant them right now,
the flowers will bloom in three to four months
I can make them bloom right now before your eyes,
using a spell
But...
I'm very slow
I want to slowly watch them sprout
and bloom
Will you wait for them to bloom with me?
Of course
I...
I will go through life with you slowly
This gift will only hinder them
Thank you. We'll eat everything
Thank you
Have you seen it?
This ahjusshi was crying
I've never seen adults cry with snot
He's probably sick
Do you think so?
Are you okay?
I brought you some medicine
Here
As soon as the shaman Choi's brother speaks,
we can catch Jin Mu
I need to ask Jin Moo something
My father himself decided to become a nomad
or was there some story behind it?
Only he knows
Stargazer Cho Chun died because of Chang Gang's Gwangju
Stargazer Cho learned that Gwangju used witchcraft
For fear that everything will be revealed,
Jin Mu made him a nomad and he went wild
This means
that we killed an innocent person?
It's not our fault
We didn't know the whole story
Everyone thinks
that astrologer Cho killed his family because he became interested in witchcraft
Gwangju asked to clear Cho Chun's name
We will discuss this at the next Unified Council
But why did Jin Mu go so far?
If he wanted to keep Cho Chun silent,
why did he turn it
into a soul swallower and forced to kill the whole family?
Jin Mu knew everything
about the circumstances of Chan Wook's birth
He did it
with Chang Gan's friend, Cho Chun,
just to torment Chang Gang
This means
that if Jin Moo is caught, he will give up
Mr Chan's secret
We can't allow this to happen. Jin Mu
must die
If you place a curse on soul reflectors, then
you can control the soul that uses it
You can make him go wild
and then get rid of it when it petrifies
Shaman Choi
placed a curse on all the soul reflectors she created
That's why I haven't become a nomad to this day
I'll force all the nomads
in this capital to run wild, just like Cho Chun did that day
Deputy,
Chan Wook is about to leave Jeongjingak
Will Pine Forest let him go?
These are the rumors
They say he is leaving the capital
Will he leave everything?
Chan Wook is my only weapon against the prince. If he leaves...
There's nothing you can offer me
deputy gwangju
Why does he leave Sosnovy Bor?
He drank poison to get there, took possession of Chisu
Maybe he even has the power of the stone,
so why?
Maybe he has changed?
This means he has changed
Why did he change so suddenly?
What made him change?
People change because of other people
Find out who appeared just at the moment when he began to change
This will be the answer
I came for Nak Soo's sword
It can't be. It couldn't be Nak Soo
He used Tansu, which was owned by Nak Su
No...
He probably learned this from Master Li
I saw everything while I was with him in Danhyangok
and there was no one with him except his maid
Is he leaving with his maid?
Yes
He takes Moo Deok with him, who follows him everywhere.
Sorry for bringing you here
You said that you need to buy a lot of things
I'll help
If she is who I think she is...
Moo Deok?
-Are you okay?
- Yes
Didn't you hear me calling you?
I heard
Why didn't I answer?
Did you also hear the ringing of bells?
Bells? I haven't heard
- They're not very good, let's go
- Okay
Nak Su,
you gave me hope
Master Li, there's one over there
Eh, what are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Master Li, you've missed so many fish
I don't regret the fish I didn't catch
What does this mean?
Then it's a waste of time
Otherwise it's greed and obsession
- What?
- However,
I realized that in loss there is pure sadness.
Lately I'm starting to understand why people are sad
when they see the flow of water,
the passing season and the setting sun
Looking at this empty cart makes me sad
Moo Deok said to catch a lot of fish
So will you leave the nomad by your side?
We kept our promise to you
Nak Soo pointed her sword at me,
and then dropped it
So I hope you keep your end of the deal and let us go
What happened to the ice stone that day?
Could it be inside you?
Even so,
he is absolutely useless
I can't even control a drop of water, let alone a Goldfish
If you start training again, you will be able to use this power
I saw how the desire to master this power
made people cruel and evil
It's better not to awaken the power of the ice stone
You're greedy for fish
don't you care about the ice stone?
You're better than me
Anyway, as long as I have the ice stone,
I can protect one person
If Moo Deok goes wild,
help me use this power to stop this
She'll be fine as long as she doesn't try to show her power.
This weak body hides the powerful soul of a killer
If anything had happened, she would have gone wild by now.
She didn't go wild because
that her body is controlled by the power of her soul
I realized this when we first met
The only thing comparable to the power of a magician is
these are the divine powers of the priestesses
I think Moo Deok's body originally belonged to
someone with divine powers
This will help relieve the pain
It will only make it easier, but will not get rid of it.
I have to give it to him
You dug your own grave
Dared to deceive me, pretending to be my daughter,
So Yi?
You weren't deceived
You knew but you pretended
Is it because of the ice stone?
Yes
A mother always recognizes her child
Until you loose your tongue,
better to kill you here and now
So you and this
do you recognize?
Boo Young was wearing this headband when she went missing.
You said you embroidered it yourself
Where did you get this?
Did Jin Mu give this to you?
No
Only I know who its real owner is
Tell me
Your daughter is still alive
Kill me
and you will never see her again
I'll keep you alive
Where is my daughter?
Don't rush me
I'll tell you when I'm sure I'm safe
The ice stone has disappeared
But there remained nomads, who were created by brother and sister Choi
and their organization
Sosnovy Bor and Jinyeowon will destroy them all
I'm asking for your help
You ask me
didn't protect Jin Mu even if he gets caught?
I know he was your teacher, but I believe that you are not blinded by him
So do you trust me?
Then you believe
that I was born under the star of the King and removed the barrier?
The ice stone barrier was lifted and you were there
Then the King's star shone
'Cause like everyone else, I believe that a star has shone upon you
I wasn't alone here that day
You stood there
Who would notice someone else besides you?
Chan Wook was there, I'm sure you saw him
He's like a son to me
You saved his life, Your Majesty
I'm truly grateful for this
Today I am leaving Sosnovy Bor
I leave my work here
You went through so much to get this job.
It's a shame you're leaving because of the wedding.
On the other hand, you will become the lady of the Chang family
Moo Deok, congratulations on your wedding
Be happy
Let's do it now. Let's go
Why are you standing there? Follow me
Your Highness, thank you for saving my life
I hope the King's star will shine forever
That's enough. No need to pretend
Awkward
You know it was Chan Wook who saved everyone that day
As you two agreed, I won't tell a living soul.
So don't worry
Do you think I'm worried about losing fame?
I'm just annoyed by everyone's flattery
They all praise you
You can just accept this praise
It's unpleasant to hear flattery from strangers, but...
When you thank me, knowing the whole truth,
It seems like you're kidding me. Annoying
I understand that you are uncomfortable
You'll never see me again
So don't worry
I heard
-You're leaving with him
- Yes
We're going to move away from here and live together
Together?
I could easily stop you from leaving
Do you think I'll let him go?
when he knows my weakness?
And if we stay close, how will you feel?
It won't end with just irritation
Yes
Won Moo Deok, you listened to my petty complaints
Listen to this too
I'll feel worthless knowing that he did what I couldn't.
And by pretending that it's all my fault, I'll become even more pathetic.
But most of all
I will fiercely despise...
seeing both of you together
I already said
I don't hold on to what I can't hold on to
Do you know what will happen if I try to hold someone and I can’t?
You will blame this man
and get rid of it?
If self-pity turns into cruelty or anger,
avoiding me won't fix anything
Go so far that I
couldn't get you
Guys,
I'm getting married tomorrow!
You boys
We won't see each other that often anymore
Of course not
Cho Young wouldn't let that happen
- Neither his mother-in-law
- Exactly
He won't come again
ride horses
Or go fishing with us
I will find time to see you
And how? Are you going to lie about training?
Were you seriously planning to lie to the priestess of Jinyeowon?
He will be caught immediately
She will surround you with her relics
and demand the truth
Then you confess everything
They'll pluck out all his hair
Let's start with the fact that he has thin hair
I understand
Are you jealous of me
I'm still happy
I'm marrying my first love
I give you, bachelors, my good energy
- Caught
- Yes, you have Moo Deok
- Yes
-But she's not your first love
- Is she already the eighth?
- No... no... no
- Just don't tell her that.
- Okay
Okay, we'll leave you alone
Yul, you can take my energy
No need
I was recently rejected
What?
Who?
Moo Deok?
No
I didn't have feelings for her
Then who is it?
Uk, do you know?
Well I have my guesses
Have you decided where you're going yet, Chan Wook?
Village of Sari. I want to know something
Are you ready to return to Soho Fortress?
You're leaving right after my wedding, right?
A little later I think
I haven't recovered yet
Does it still hurt?
I heard that the wound has already healed
What? Is Master Huo a charlatan?
The wound has healed
but it still hurts me
I'll be fine
Mr. So Yul
I don't know if I should give this to you
But one beggar asked me to give
This medicine will relieve chest pain
You have to accept it
This person knows about my condition
Who is this?
I knew you would return, Your Highness
Chan Wook is exhausted, I'll send him away from here
He doesn't have an ice stone
Confess your crimes by the end of the day
If you don't do this,
I will catch you and punish you myself
Everyone is deceiving you
Have you seen the head of Sosnovy Bor today?
What did he say?
Were you delighted that a star was shining above you?
He knows it was Chan Wook and not you
So is Master Li.
He broke into the palace
and mentioned the King's star
Are you saying that everyone is deceiving me and mocking me?
They are trying to protect Chan Wook
The stone belongs to the one for whom the star shines
and Sosnovy Bor protects him
Only I can protect you
Chan Wook is keeping a big secret
I'll expose him...
and...
I'll make you sink to the bottom
That's it...
Who drank it all?
Your cup is empty
Was it you? You drank it all
If the cup is empty, pour me more
- That's it
- Have a drink
"Have a drink"? How dare you?
- “Have a drink”?..
- To the bottom
Oh, it's our young master!
We celebrated something today
- Her departure from Sosnovy Bor
- I see
- Hello, Chan Wook
- Hey!
He's your young master
I'm sorry. My mistake
- That's right
- They drank too much
Young Master
Come here
I'll show you something amazing
When Moo Deok is drunk
she doesn't speak dialect
Amazing, right?
I can't
show something really worthwhile
But I can fly to the roof
Really? Try it
- Should I try?
- Try it
Look closely
Just a second
- Moo Deok...
- Doesn't work
Sit down
Can't do it anymore
And I can’t draw my sword
What? This?
It's not yours. This is Nak Soo's sword
- Young Master
- Yes?
Why did you bring this garbage again?
I'll get rid of him
Give me one more chance
- Of course, try it
- Sit down
Fly, do it
- Clean up here and go to sleep
-Did you see this?
- I'll deal with Moo Deok
- I can fly
- Don't move
- It worked
She really flew
Chief, did you see this?
I want to fly too
You kids have no idea who I am
I'm the master here. Do you want me to show you?
I'm the master here
Today is just not my day
Moo Deok
Never drink again. You will tell everyone that you are Nak Soo
I have to tell you something
Sleep, you'll tell me tomorrow
Need it today
What if I die tomorrow without telling you anything?
Okay, speak up. Suddenly die
I'm listening
Chan Wook
I like you very much
Yeah, and went straight to bed
Just like that
We need to tell her what Master Li said
I think Moo Deok's body originally belonged to
someone with divine powers
Maybe I'll find out when I get to the village of Sari
Let bygones be bygones
Now you will become relatives
Cho Young does not join the Park family
This is Dan Gu becoming part of our
He's not moving in with you
You say things like that and people gossip
that Park Dan Gu will soon become Jin Dan Gu
Their daughters will give our last name
And our son - ours
Don't argue on this wonderful day
Guests will arrive soon
Be ready to greet them
Come on
Where is Dan Gu?
He will go to Saejukwon with Jo Young first
They want to get to her father and say hello
Where is Moo Deok?
Don't know. She came first, but I didn't see her
Is she embarrassed and avoiding me because of last night?
Nak Su,
you can't draw your sword because you're stuck in this body
You are my last weapon
I'll use all my strength to call yours
As soon as you get your strength back,
you're going wild
Only I know who its real owner is
Your daughter is still alive
Mother
Maid Kim
Where did your maid Moo Deok used to live?
Are her parents alive?
No. She comes from the village of Sari
When she was accused of So Yi's crimes,
I told you everything
I asked you to help this poor girl
But you didn't help
Does So Yi know Moo Deok?
Yes. Ms. Cho Young knows her too
You are incredibly beautiful
I can say the same about you
Let's say hello to your father
You can't stay here for long
If the elders find out, they will sit on their ears
Yes
Thank you
mu... husband
Be careful
well... wife
My wife
Wait
Moo Deok? Why are you here?
Moo Deok, you can't bring the sword
Kill Jin Woo Tak first
Moo Dok!
What's happening?
You
Chan Wook's maid?
Are you okay?
Kill Jin Woo Tak
Father!
Moo Deok,
what are you doing?
She...
She's a mercenary
Run, Cho Young
Hurry up!
Mister!
Stop Moo Deok
Moo Deok
Stop her!
No...
Kill her! Rather
Father!
Father
Don't die
Dad, please...
Dad
Dad don't die
Nak Su,
kill those who did this to your father
Dad!
How dare you appear here?
Catch Jin Mu!
I, Deputy of Gwangju,
came to catch the nomad
Nak Su, nomad, now in Sosnovy Bor
- Nak Soo?
- Head!
Trouble!
Mercenary appeared in Sejukwon
She killed Mr. Jin
This is the mercenary I'm looking for. Nak Soo
No
This...
It was Moo Deok
This Moo Deok is Nak Soo
Mercenary!
Mercenary in Saejukwon!
Catch her!
- Catch it!
- Eat!
Moo Deok
Chan Wook?
It's me?
It's me
I pierced you
One
I will hold your hand in the ring of my arms
No one has a ring like this
If I become Nak Soo, I'll be in danger
It shouldn't concern you what happens to me then
Why?
Because we will no longer be student and teacher?
You'll have no reason to protect me
And I have reasons to be gentler with you
This was our promise
Then promise me one more thing
When you get your strength back,
if you have to raise a sword on someone,
let me be the first
If you pierce me,
I will die to the one who released the mercenary
Chan Wook!
No...
Catch her!
Uk...
Uk!
I think
Wook knew that Moo Deok was Nak Soo
Jin Mu
looking for evidence of this in Jeonjingak as we speak
I knew it too
Let me go after her
and find out what happened
You are the eldest son of the So family
You didn't know anything
From now on you are not allowed to leave this place.
Father died
at the hands of a mercenary
I'll find
and I'll kill her
No
You must find her and bring her back alive.
Nak Soo is only a soul in this body
I have to find out who this body belonged to.
Bring her back at any cost
Nak Su practiced soul alchemy
along with the Choi family
I've caught her before
when he killed all her people
That's why I knew that Nak Soo was still alive
I've been looking for her all this time
to clear your name
And she's a daughter
Cho Chun, killed by the main families?
She probably entered Sosnovy Bor to avenge her father.
Chang Gang's son kept her close, knowing who she was?
He's dead, we won't know
But I hope that you will punish Sosnovy Bor for everything
Where is Nak Soo?
The magicians of Jeonbugwan are looking for her
She started to run wild, soon she will turn into stone and die
Moo Deok
Chan Wook!
I can't mourn, I can't bury him
properly, since he is a criminal
How can he be cremated this way?
This is not possible!
Stop them...
Sosnovy Bor
has no voice
in this matter
I'm sorry
Mister...
Why am I here?
At least...
I can no longer hear the sound of bells
Nak Su will go to the grave of the nomads
There he will meet his death
Born under the star of the King, you have the power of heaven.
This is not how you are destined to die,
Chan Wook
Mister
Thanks for watching with us!
doramamania
Alchemy
Shower